st-patricks-day.com 2006-06-18

# www.St-Patricks-Day.com

**ABOUT US  
**  
St-Patricks-Day.com may be just another day in the year, but it is also synonymous with Ireland and possibly the strongest Irish brand in existence. St. Patrick's Day is a time when the whole world becomes Irish and in particular the Irish diaspora thinks of visiting the ol' sod & "the folks back home", and quite possibly... the best time for selling & enhancing your brand internationally. 

Now in its 9th year, St-Patricks-Day.com, the number one ranking information website for this internationally famous day, has been relaunched as a perfect vehicle for companies aiming to capitalise on the world-wide media exposure of the "Irish".

The objective of St-Patricks-Day.com is to become the world's largest online resource for Irish nationals and Irish diaspora with the bulk of the audience being Irish Americans, Irish Diaspora and people interested in Ireland.

Email Us re. Advertising, Marketing, PR & Sales promotion opportunities at [info@st-patricks-day.com](mailto:info@st-patricks-day.com)

**PRIVACY POLICY  
**St-Patricks-Day.com Internet Promotions is committed to protecting our users privacy. To that end, we offer this statement to inform our users of how we define, gather and utilize personal information.  
**  
** St-Patricks-Day.com Internet Promotions reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter this policy at any time. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued usage of the St-Patricks-Day.com website following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute your acceptance of the revised privacy policy. For your information, this page was last updated on July 28th 2001.

We define personal information as information that includes a person's full name, address, telephone number, date of birth and/or email address or any other information that is tied to individually identifiable information that would allow someone to identify or contact you, unless stated otherwise herein or on the Site. We can gather information on our users in by two different methods: cookie technology and voluntary submissions.

We utilise cookie technology to collect data regarding the number of visits a person has made to our site and also for personalisation purposes. This data is stored in aggregate form and is in no way singled out in an individual file. This information allows us to know what pages/sites are of interest to our users and what pages/sites may be of less interest. Such information is utilized in revising the website to better meet our users needs and interests.

We also collect personally identifiable information from users through voluntary submissions. We use good faith efforts to make it clear why the information is being collected and what it will be used for. In the event that this information is being shared with a third party affiliate, sponsor or advertiser, we will use good faith efforts to post a notice on the Site clearly stating that the information is being shared.

When you order products from us, we also collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or services, we will collect and maintain your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address and a password.

We collect this, and other information, as disclosed in this policy, in order to complete your order, to communicate with you about your order and to send you promotional materials. Before confirming your order, you will have the opportunity to review the product order form and make changes and additions to the information it contains. These changes will be automatically kept for future use. We use every effort not to provide third parties with access to your individual account information, unless stated otherwise on the Site. We reserves the right to provide non-identifiable consumer data to third parties including, but not limited to, general statistics about pages viewed on our site, sales and other shopping information.

We have taken steps to ensure that personally identifiable information collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to its database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access.

St-Patricks-Day.com Internet Promotions would like to take this opportunity to encourage users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom to release information online. All queries should be sent to [info@st-patricks-day.com](mailto:info@st-patricks-day.com)
